Hrushikesh Thakur

Address: A4/ 104 Vaishnavi Dham CHS., Kharegaon, Kalwa, Thane.

Phone: +91 9167082723
Email: hrushiathakur@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Looking for a job in an organization which will provide me an opportunity to utilize & improve my skills and knowledge as a Developer. I have experience of 2 years working in the Software Industry which I am eager to apply in new and upcoming challenges.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Analyst/ Software Engineer Capgemini, Airoli

11/2022 - Present

- In October 2022 I was promoted to Analyst position.
- Along with ServiceNow, from November 2022 I am also working on the Robotic Process Automation (UiPath).

03/2021 - 10/2022

Software Associate Capgemini, Airoli

- Working in Capgemini as a Software associate on the ServiceNow ITSM tool to provide service to projects across Europe.
- Also working as a backup Business Analyst from July 2022 for ServiceNow.

EDUCATION

2021 - 2022

MSc. Information Technology University of Mumbai, **8.48 CGPA**

2017 - 2020

BSc. Information Technology University of Mumbai, **6.92 CGPA**

SKILLS

Front-end: ReachJS, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Material UI

Scripting: JavaScript, jQuery **Back-end:** Java, Spring Boot, PHP

Database operation: MySQL, PostgreSQL

Other: Agile, ServiceNow

Certification: AWS Certified Cloud Practitioner.

SOCIAL PROFILES

GitHub: github.com/hrushi99

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/hrushikesh-thakur-276704182

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Bus Ticket Booking System: This project is a website which can be used to book bus tickets online with the use of GUI based seat booking.

Booksbadlo.com: This project is a website which can be used to buy all kinds of books from other users.

Progress Inspector Developed with ReactJS and Java Spring Boot, this project Progress Inspector is a Work from home monitoring system which will help team leader to check the progress of developers on the assigned tasks. The team leader can create and assign task, clients can approve tasks.